(This program is intended
for viewers aged 18 and over.)
(It may contain content
depicting inappropriate behavior)
(violence, sexual content,
and strong language.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(This series is entirely fictional
and does not depict)
(any real individuals, locations,
organizations, or events.)
I really do like you.
Oh, Soh.
I'm sorry.
My intrusive thoughts just won.
I'm such a jerk.
I was totally taking advantage
of the moment.
Do you...
really like me, P'Three?
If you're still not sure,
you don't have to like me back yet.
But can I ask you one thing?
Please don't run away from me again.
Don't run away from my feelings
that I have only for you.
Or...
have you not forgiven me
for what just happened?
Soh, I'm sorry. I mean...
You can scold me or even punch me.
I'll take whatever you throw at me.
P'Three...
Please open your eyes.
I'm not going to punch you,
and I never thought
about running away, either.
Since you didn't say anything,
my heart literally sank.
To be honest,
I'm feeling pretty awkward, too.
You suddenly told me you like me.
Then...
shall we take things one step at a time?
You can take your time to think.
You don't have to
give me an answer right away.
Let's play a game instead.
What kind of game?
The game of winning Derpy Kid's heart.
I'll make everything clear.
You can try
the one-week free trial first
before giving me your answer.
If you're down,
the start button is right here.
I'm just kidding.
You don't have to press it just yet.
Keep it as my reward
for when I win this game.
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Every time, it's just me and me only♪
♪What's this feeling? I've got no clue,♪
♪Could it be I'm missing you?♪
♪(Am I missing you?)♪
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Why is it always happening to me?♪
♪The more it happens, the more I see♪
♪Yeah, it must be♪
You can try
the one-week free trial first.
If you're down,
the start button is right here.
P'Three, help me!
Help me, please.
Your knight in shining armor
is on his way.
What?
Where the hell are you going?
I'm dead.
Well...
Whoa,
excuse me, Son of Wanphen.
My Carry had one bar of HP left,
but you were busy
helping the full-HP Support?
Are you here to play for B.S. Brothers
or just Soh, huh?
You guys need to stop whining.
I'll treat you to mookrata, okay?
You threw the game so hard
you owe me a salmon buffet.
Whoa, you're getting real sneaky.
You're getting good
at taking advantage of the chaos.
Hey, our team won three games already.
We've got the momentum now.
- So...
- We've gotta keep pushing!
I think we should take a break.
- What?
Look, let me tell you something.
Our team's HP
is running pretty low right now.
We're in terrible form,
and the tournament
has been dragging on for so long.
I think you guys should rest,
and while you're resting,
don't let your HP drop
as low as it did in the game, got it?
From the look of it,
he just wants to go
on a honeymoon with P'Jane.
You've got a big mouth, Laem,
acting like you're...
living under my bed or something.
Fine. Since that's
the attitude you want to take,
forget the break. Keep practicing.
- What? No! We need a break.
- Whoa, chill. Please give us a break.
You and your big mouth.
Anyway, I'll see you guys next week.
See you then, P'Three.
Hey, wait a sec, Soh.
I found this really cute game.
You should give it a try.
Is it an FPS? What kind of game is it?
Kind...
of normal.
No download needed.
I'll send you the link.
Does it have to be right now?
Not right now, but you have to play it.
Don't bail on me,
or I'll be really upset.
Okay.
I'll give it a try.
You promised.
I'm off, then.
Make sure to play it.
Catch you later.
(Winning Derpy Kid's Heart)
(Someone wants to
spend their day off with you.)
(Will you give them a chance
to go on a date?)
What are you doing, P'Three?
Hello, ma boy.
Stunned, aren't you?
I know I'm incredibly handsome,
and I know I'm looking super hot today.
You do look handsome,
but whose car is this?
Get in. Come on.
(Three hours ago)
Yes!
What should we do?
Watch a movie?
What should we watch? What's out now?
Hold on.
A meal?
My dearest brother, Four.
Your favorite brother
needs a little favor.
Hey there, little brother.
Wow, I missed you so much.
Come here!
- There, there. Let's hug. I missed you.
- Don't touch me.
- Go away.
- What?
Stop faking it.
As if you ever wanted to hug me.
Don't expose me like that.
The key.
- What?
- Give me the key.
Here.
Dad's been wanting you
to come pick it up forever.
It's just cluttering the place.
Cluttering?
Fine, I'll keep it, then.
You little brat, come here!
Jeez, leave me alone.
Where did you get these looks from?
- Me, obviously. Come here.
- Go away.
Let me go. I've got plans for dinner.
- Dinner?
- Yeah.
Are you dating someone?
Show me their Insta. Let me see it.
Mind your own business.
As if you ever cared.
Are you mad at me?
You wish.
Fine.
Anyway, if you ever have any problems,
you can always
tell your big brother, kid.
Maybe worry about yourself first.
I'm doing just fine.
Bye.
Wait, want a ride?
- No, I already called one.
- Oh, you don't want a ride from me?
- Nah.
- Okay, then. See ya.
Ouch!
Where are we going, P'Three?
I'll keep it under wraps for now.
I want it to be a surprise.
I kinda thought
you wouldn't agree to come.
Do you have any idea
how long it took me to code that game?
I barely got any sleep.
Was the coding the hard part?
It was choosing
my best-looking photo. Hey!
You really jumped there just now.
P'Three, watch out!
Roger that.
You don't have to worry
because ever since I started driving,
I've never had a single accident.
- Watch out!
- Whoa!
Are you even driving?
Where are you going, the moon?
Soh, are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Did you hit your head?
Are you in any pain?
I'm so sorry.
I should've been more careful.
- It's my fault that...
- I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
If anything hurts,
you need to tell me.
I'm seriously okay.
A little damage like this
is nothing to a Support like me.
Let's get going.
I'm dying to know
where you're taking me.
You're sure you're not hurt anywhere?
I'm not hurt.
Please have a seat.
Here's the menu, sir.
You can order whatever you want.
Do you have any recommendations?
How about...
Escargot Louboutin?
I'll have this one.
Certainly.
Thank you.
Do you come here often?
It's my regular spot.
Usually, it's incredibly hard
to get a reservation here.
But for you,
it was a breeze.
I always order this dish
when I come here.
Is this your go-to meal?
It is.
This is my absolute favorite,
Escargot Louboutin...
You make it look so delicious.
Here.
I think I'll just go
with a salad instead.
One salad, please.
You're not having the Louboutin?
(Thought you said you'd tell me
about your old friend.)
(Man, you're so nosy.)
(If you're this curious, come to me
and I'll tell you.)
(Fine by me. We'll finally meet.)
(Where at?)
(How about Bananax2?)
(Then hurry up. Last one there pays.)
Actually, this place
offers a special performance, too.
I'm sure you're going to love it.
Really?
Cheers.
Okay.
Sh...
Sh*t.
We're really sorry, sir.
Good thing they're okay.
As cute as ever.
We're really sorry, sir.
We're going to bring you a new cake.
It's fine. I'm cutting back
on sugar anyway.
This is already sweet enough.
Please.
Do you like it?
Uh, I mean...
do you like our first date?
Well, aside from the mishap,
the food and the vibe
were pretty good.
Well,
I like it.
Being this close,
it's easy to tell what you're thinking.
I don't think I'm cut out
for dates like this.
I'm feeling a bit nervous.
Right?
I've been trying so hard to act cool.
You're not the only one.
I'm nervous, too.
This is my first time
eating at a place like this, too.
I usually just go for mala hotpot.
I don't want our first date
to end in disappointment.
Can I restart
the game of winning your heart?
(Winning Derpy Kid's Heart)
Then from now on,
don't take me
to do anything too fancy.
It was so fancy I got all nervous.
I promise.
No more escargot snails
or orchestras or whatever.
Let's go.
How did you know I wanted to come here?
Well, you see,
I happened to see someone
liking a video about capybaras.
Wow, I'm so attentive,
aren't I?
By the way, why did you want
to come to the zoo?
Do you like animals?
Yes, I do.
Good thing my friends
call me an animal, too. Do you like me?
What did you say?
Oh, sorry.
It was just an intrusive thought.
Do you come here often?
I used to come here a lot
with my parents,
but I haven't been back
since my dad passed away.
It's nice being at the zoo today.
Feels like going back in time.
Then let's be kids again.
I'll do everything
just like your dad used to,
though I probably
won't be as good as him.
Anyway, whatever you wanna do
or wherever you wanna go,
just let me know. I'll make it happen.
Mom, look.
He even has a bodyguard. So cool.
Don't point at him. Sorry.
Would you like something cold
to drink, Young Master?
Shall we go
find something cold to drink?
Let's go.
Alright.
Look, P'Three!
Hey, what do you mean? I'm right here.
No, I was just pointing.
Believe it or not, I never came
to the zoo when I was a kid.
No way.
I'm serious.
Are you pulling my leg?
When I was little, my parents always
made me watch the gold shop,
so I never got to go out.
That's why I grew up being a homebody.
Actually, a gamer.
Just like you.
You've got it all over your mouth.
P'Three,
that's WuKong.
- What skin...
- Mini WuKong.
Mini WuKong?
What skin is this?
Everyone who plays WuKong
is handsome, though.
Hey, are you complimenting yourself?
Oh, you can tell?
Believe it or not,
I used to travel quite a lot back then.
I wasn't the homebody nerd
you think I was.
That's nice.
So you traveled with your family?
Yes, my dad loved
taking me to other provinces.
I've been everywhere.
North, south, east, and west.
My dad used to say I was very cute
with my chubby cheeks.
So he took a ton of photos of me
'cause he knew I wouldn't be as cute
once I grew up.
If your dad ever came to me in a dream,
I'd tell him myself
that you're still just as cute
now that you're grown up.
Since you've grown up this much,
can I take a photo of you now?
- Sure.
- Great, come here.
- Come on. Oh, look. He's right here.
- Whoa.
Right. How am I supposed to see them?
Hey, P'Three!
What are you doing?
Did you see the sloth yet?
- Yeah, he's huge.
- Want another look?
One, two, three.
- You actually look like them.
- You, too.
- I don't.
- You do.
- No, I don't.
- Check the photo.
Cute.
So, what's your type?
Do you have a type?
I haven't really thought about that yet.
Hey, no worries.
I don't have a type, either.
As long as I'm comfortable
being around them, that's enough.
You're answering like a celebrity.
Hey, I'm a famous streamer, you know.
Whoa, P'Three!
Look at its face.
It's just like the video I saw.
The ears are twitching.
Shall we take a selfie?
Of course.
Excuse me.
Are you P'Three from B.S. Brothers?
Yes, I am.
Can I take a photo with you?
Sure, come on.
Guys, come on. He said yes!
- Yay!
Wait...
Look, Doraemon!
- Oh, P'Three...
- Hey, P'Three!
Hey!
Wait!
- P'Three!
P'Three!
You can go take photos
with them first, P'Three.
I can wait.
I don't want to.
If anything, I'm already late.
I should've just
carried you away sooner.
Today is our first date.
I want to be your P'Three,
not everyone else's Thr33Gamer.
If things keep going like this,
I guess our date is over.
Or...
do you want to head back now?
I'd like to stay
just a little bit longer.
I told you not to run.
P'Three!
They're leaving.
I know what we're gonna do now.
(I got here first, so it's your treat.)
(Yeah, fine. Order whatever you want.)
(Get the paprika fried bananas for me.)
(I'm almost there.)
There are people
who still eat something like this?
I'll have the paprika fried bananas
and an iced Americano.
Certainly. Please wait a moment.
Our fates must be intertwined, huh?
Met you again.
I'm in a good mood.
Could you please not ruin it?
I'd like to help,
but I'm meeting someone here, too.
Can I ruin your good mood
for a bit, then?
Be my guest.
But go sit at another table.
Let's keep to ourselves.
One iced latte, less sugar, please.
Certainly. Just a moment.
(Which table are you at?)
(New message)
(The first table.
You'll see me as soon as you walk in.)
(New message)
Here are your paprika fried bananas.
It's you?
Why?
Are you disappointed
that the friend
who's always listened to your problems
and said goodnight
to you every night is me?
Seriously,
how much longer
are you going to mess with my head?
Is it really that fun
to play with my feelings?
Who said I was playing?
So you're saying that all this time,
you were actually being sincere with me?
I don't know.
Figure it out yourself.
You're an expert
at jumping to conclusions anyway.
What's the point of me saying anything?
P'Three, where did you go?
Probably not him.
He must have gone home already.
That was a close call.
What's this?
A bear with a monkey face?
And I'm a monkey with a bear face?
Really?
I'm sorry.
I must have panicked
and mixed them up.
You're a derpy kid through and through.
You can just be a bear, then.
Hey, no way.
I don't want to steal the spotlight
from the bear-head gamer.
I'm sorry, Soh.
The game of winning your heart
wasn't fun at all, was it?
Nothing went as planned.
In my head, I imagined
a super romantic date.
Look at how it turned out.
Taking you to eat snails,
and when I finally brought you
where you wanted to come,
we got interrupted again.
I wouldn't be surprised
if the game was over today.
You asked me earlier
what my type was.
Actually, I've never really had a type.
But today, I've realized
exactly what my type is.
My type...
is someone who's hot-tempered and loud.
(Are you even driving?)
- But when he's serious,
- (Where are you going, the moon?)
he's the most reliable person.
He might seem a bit unfriendly
and be a bit of a show-off.
(It's my regular spot.)
(Usually, it's incredibly hard
to get a reservation here.)
But he's actually very kind.
He's down-to-earth
and not a picky eater at all.
Even though he says
he doesn't like cute things,
if it's something I like,
he ends up humoring me anyway.
Whenever I'm with him,
I feel like I've become a kid again.
- Oh, P'Three...
- Hey, P'Three!
So,
even if today didn't go as planned
or wasn't as perfect as you expected,
I just want to tell you that
I'm very happy,
and I had a lot of fun.
Plus, I got to see another side of you,
one that isn't just Thr33Gamer
or a big brother.
I mean,
are you just lying
to make me feel better?
I don't lie. I keep the Five Precepts.
Then let's...
go see Moo Deng, shall we?
Sure. I want to see her.
Well, before we go see Moo Deng,
the bouncy hippo,
can I...
see your bouncy hips first?
Come on, what are you talking about?
Hey, why?
I won't let you.
Hey, your cheeks
are bouncy and squishy, too.
I guess I don't have to ask
if you had a good time today.
I'm just so happy
that you're no longer running away
from my feelings for you.
And now, when my birthday comes around,
what gift could possibly top
how I feel today?
How is that my fault?
By the way,
when is your birthday?
Christmas Day. Cool, right?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Then it's coming up pretty soon.
Is there anything you want as a gift?
Nothing too expensive, please.
I need to save up first.
There's actually something I want,
and it's not expensive.
I definitely won't rob you.
It's something that
you can give me.
But if you don't tell me,
I'll never know.
Come to my room, then you'll find out.
I'm heading off, then.
(BS.THR33 wants to be your Lover.
I'll protect you.)
Hey.
You came all the way to my place
just to give me sh*t?
Are you obsessed
with getting sh*t from me or what?
Then why did you come here?
To make me pay for the bananas?
My mom told me to give this back to you.
I'm leaving.
Wait, Jack.
I just realized something.
Tomorrow is Sunday.
Wanna come up for a few drinks?
This room of yours
never changes, does it?
Nothing but booze.
Still no water.
Why bother drinking water?
It's pointless.
And what about you?
What made you agree
to drink with me tonight?
I thought you'd hate me
to the point of wanting me dead.
To me,
you're already dead.
One shot, and you're done.
I've killed you
thousands of times in the game,
but in the end,
I resurrect you every single time.
You know what?
I can't die,
at least not in your memories.
And you know what else?
If we finish this all at once,
we won't remember a thing until morning.
Why's that?
What happens when morning comes?
You and I might just go back
to hating each other
and forget all about today.
Just wait and see
what happens tomorrow morning
- between you and me.
- Then stay with me until then.
Fine.
I will.
(Hey, happy...)
(Christmas!)
(Soh, guess what day it is.)
It's...
Christmas Day.
Soh, today is my birthday.
I'm actually getting mad.
I know it's your birthday.
I was just messing with you.
(You're so nice,)
(not like those B.S. Brothers guys.)
They never remember my birthday.
(Since it's my birthday today,)
shall we go celebrate?
I'm sorry, P'Three.
Actually, I'm busy...
I have...
a final project to finish.
Come on, it's a special day.
Are we really not going to
celebrate it together?
Please? Stay with me, please.
Or...
should I come to you?
No, you can't!
You can't.
I have to go...
shopping.
Yeah.
Yeah, shopping.
(Shopping?)
I thought you were doing a project.
I'm buying stuff for the final project.
Call me when you're free, then.
I'll be waiting.
As for the birthday gift I asked for,
no rush. Take your time.
It's okay if it's a bit late.
Even 15 minutes late is fine.
Okay.
I'll go buy the gift... Wait, no.
I'll go buy things for the project now,
okay?
Okay.
Soh,
was the last time you lied
back in second grade?
Am I going to get caught?
What should I do?
He won't suspect a thing.
He thinks you're purely derpy.
He'd never think
you'd play him like that.
That almost sounds like an insult.
Do you guys have any idea
what P'Three wants?
You, obviously.
We should finish this quickly,
so we can go shopping.
If we're any later,
he's going to be really upset.
Let's eat.
Do you know what he wants, though?
How should I know?
You should've asked this guy.
You've been with him lately.
What does he like?
I don't know.
If I knew,
I wouldn't be asking you guys.
How would I know?
Okay.
You have the key?
Yeah.
It's not the first time
I've been to his place.
Let's go.
Happy Birthday, P'Three!
Hey, P'Three! Merry Christmas...
Soh...
♪Happy birthday to you♪
♪Happy birthday, happy birthday♪
- Soh, I...
- Blow out the candles first.
This salmon is amazing.
We already ate some before we came here,
so I'm pretty stuffed.
It feels like I'm going to burst.
- Soh...
- P'Three...
I hope all your wishes come true.
- P'Jack, P'Laem.
- Yeah?
I have to head back
and work on my project.
I'll take my leave now.
Wait, Soh!
Soh!
Soh...
(Why do people
keep going back to their exes?)
(What is it, P'Three?)
Soh, can you open the door?
(If you don't open the door,)
(how am I supposed
to explain it to you?)
I...
I'm about to go to sleep.
(I thought you said you don't lie.)
The lights are still on.
(I know you're not going to sleep yet.)
How could you possibly know
better than I do?
Can I have just five minutes?
Just let me explain.
If after you've heard me out,
you want me to leave,
I'll leave.
Just five minutes.
I told you,
in my eyes,
you're the only one.
And right now,
Belle and I are just friends.
What happened between us
ended a long time ago.
She came to see me today
because she's going to study abroad.
She just came to say goodbye
and wish me a happy birthday.
Before you arrived,
she was bragging about her new guy,
talking about
how great he is and all that.
He's probably better than me.
She wouldn't stop praising him.
Are you jealous?
It's not exactly jealousy.
I just don't like
being compared to anyone.
Try to imagine
if I like someone else one day...
Can you just not like someone else?
I don't even want to think about
you liking someone else.
How...
How could I like someone else
when the person I like
is standing right here in front of me?
I still want to play that game with you.
The game you asked me
to play that night.
The one where the start button...
is right here.
But for this game,
I'm the only person
you're allowed to play with.
(In a relationship)
(Relationship established.)
(Lovers Lv.15)
♪The answer is you
whenever I ask my heart,♪
♪Can't get over you
though I try so hard♪
♪I'm afraid that
love could pull us apart♪
♪If I'm the only one
who's loving with all my heart♪
♪So many times I've rehearsed the line♪
♪To tell you that I wish you were mine,♪
♪But I turn into a coward
every time you look in my eyes♪
♪Maybe the risk is too high to take,♪
♪Just being near you
is enough for my sake,♪
♪But my heart beats so fast
that I can't fake♪
♪I'll find my way
into your heart one day,♪
♪Getting a little closer every day,♪
♪Before you even look my way,♪
♪Before you realize I'm here to stay♪
♪For now,
I'll just keep things brotherly♪
♪While caring for you secretly♪
♪I'll leave no signs for you to see♪
♪Until your heart makes room for me♪